Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/laurenmorrison1 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Sports

Media Training

Strategic Communications Counsel

Languages

French

Honors-Awards

GOLD Winner for best Social Media/ Facebook

GOLD for Best Government Website (design & creativity)

PLATNUM Winner for Best Website for Government

Best Website of the Year (Best Writing & Content)

SILVER Clio Sports Award - "Flip the Turf" campaign

Lauren Morrison

Vice President at FleishmanHillard

San Francisco, California, United States

Summary

An ambitious leader with 15 years of agency communications experience supporting global

brands within sports, consumer/lifestyle and tech industries. I've spent my

career alongside clients developing world class strategic brand narratives, crafting award-winning integrated communication campaigns, orchestrating needle-moving media strategies, fostering meaningful brand, sports and community partnerships, and launching countless consumer technology products from headphones to wearables.

Experience

FleishmanHillard 14 years 8 months

Vice President 2019 - Present (6 years)

Managing Supervisor
July 2010 - Present (14 years 8 months)
San Francisco Bay Area

Strategic Marketing and Communications: Media Relations: Social Media Strategy and Content Development: Copy writing: Sports PR and Event Planning/Management: Partnership Development: Marketing Strategy: Content Development: Influencer Relations: Website Content Development: Photo/Video Shoot Production

- o Manages and produces national media and marketing campaigns for a variety of consumer lifestyle, tech, and sports clients
- o Specializes in media relations, with a focus on consumer tech/lifestyle/ sports media, in support of consumer brand news, product launch campaigns, product reviews coverage

o Develops strategic communication plans for product announcements and news that create

awareness, strengthen brand loyalty, and increase market footprint

o Manage global cross-functional teams to meet and exceed campaign goals for product

launches and key partnership announcements

Develops creative concepts for full-service marketing, partnerships, and

advertising campaigns from ideation to implementation

o Provides copy and integrated strategy for a range of traditional, digital, and

social projects including social content, video, print, promotional/marketing

materials, and web

o Works closely with corporate, marketing, communications, digital and

creative teams to deliver a consistent brand voice and message across all

platforms and mediums

o Coordinates targeted ad buys for print, online and OOH

University of Mary Washington

Graduate Writing Advisor

April 2009 - June 2010 (1 year 3 months)

Editor: Tutor: Research Guide: Online Tutoring Specialist: APA style

Education

Virginia Tech

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), English · (2004 - 2008)